The one where they get back together.
Friends: The Reunion is a documentary film directed by Ben Winston.
The cast of Friends reunites for a once-in-a-lifetime celebration of the hit series, an unforgettable
evening filled with iconic memories, uncontrollable laughter, happy tears, and special guests.
Self, played by Jennifer Aniston.
Self, played by Courteney Cox.
Self, played by Lisa Kudrow.
Self, played by David Schwimmer.
Self, played by Matt LeBlanc.
Self, played by Matthew Perry.
Friends: The Reunion is a 2021 reunion special of the American television
sitcom Friends, and the sitcom's first feature-length film.
The special was hosted by James Corden and executive produced by the
show's cocreators, Marta Kauffman and David Crane, Kevin S.
Bright, the show's main cast, and Ben Winston (who also directed the special).
The special premiered on HBO Max on May 27, 2021.
The special sees the main cast revisit the sets of the original show (such as the Friends' apartments, the Central Perk coffee shop, and the signature water fountain), meet
with guests who appeared on the show as well as celebrity guests, do table reads and re-enactments of Friends episodes, and share behind-the-scenes footage.
It was Matthew Perry's final on-screen appearance before his death in 2023.
The film explores themes of reunion, friends, sitcom, tv series reunion.